Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material Series, 1970-1996 and undated
  - Lectures, Readings, and Presentations by Other Authors
    - Nystrom, Debra and Sydney Blair, 1991, April 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 5)
    - Oates, J.C., 1986, April 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 5)
    - Oates: partial tape, 1986, April 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - O'Connor, Tom at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Oles, Carol and Cheuse, Alan, 1988, March 12, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Packard, William: poetry class at Wesleyan, 1977, June, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Paley, Grace at Johnson State College, 1978, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Paley, Grace at Bennington, 1979, July 19, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Pieroll, Simon P., undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Pierson, Mandy, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Plumly, Stanley and Madison Bell, 1984, July 25-26, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Poster, Carol at Penn State, 1972, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Poster, Carol at USM, 1979, Sept. 19, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Poster, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Poster et al., undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Price, Reynolds: interview with Lynn Ballard, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Price, Reynolds: reading from 5 novels, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Ramke, Bin: reading, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Ramke, Bin: lecture, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Rath, Roger, undated, (2 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Rath, Roger and Norton Girault, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Robison, Mary and Alan Cheuse, 1987, July 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Robison and Cheuse, 1987, July 25, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Robison and Stephen Dunn, 1986, July 13, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Roeser, Dana and Debra Nystrom, 1984, Nov. 15, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Rogers, Tim, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Rosen, Ken at Johnson State College, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Rosen, Ken, undated, (4 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Ruefle, Mary at Bennington, 1979, Oct. 25, (2 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Rurak, Gib at Hollins, 1981, March, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sadoff, Ira at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sadoff, Ira and Andre Dubus, 1983, July 19, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sadoff, at Stonecoast, 1983, July 20, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sadoff, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Salter, James, 1991, Feb. 19, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sandy, Stephen at Cambridge, 1979, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sandy, Stephen at Johnson State College, 1979, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sandy at Bennington, 1982, July 6, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sandy at Johnson State College, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Sandy, undated, (2 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Schwartz, Lynne: lecture, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Schwartz, Lynne: reading, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Settle, Mary Lee in Blotner's Southern Lit. class at Michigan, 1983, April 5, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Settle, Mary Lee: workshop at Michigan, 1983, April 5, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, 1992, March 12, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Settle at Michigan, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Settle: reading from Strike Night, undated, (3 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Settle, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Settle and Janet Burroway at NKU, undated, (2 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Shelnett, Eve, 1975, May 6, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Shelnett, Eve, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Shrevel, Susan at Hollins, 1985, March 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Shulman, Alix at Stonecoast, 1983, July 10, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Simic, Charles, 1979, July 10, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Simic, Charles at Stonecoast, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Simpson, Mona and Jay McInerney, 1987, July 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Slavitt, David at Bennington, 1979, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Slavitt, David at Bennington, 1980, July 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Slavitt, at Bennington, 1980, July 4, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Slavitt, 1985, April 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Slavitt, at University of Virginia, 1985, April 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Slavitt: 50th Book Party, 1994, Oct. 8, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Slavitt,: reading poems, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Slavitt, and others at York Harbor, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Dave at Bennington, 1983, July 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Dave and Nicholas Delbanco, 1983, July 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Dave, 1987, Sept. 26, (3 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Lee at Hollins College, 1981, Feb. 17, (2 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Lee, 1988, May 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Lee at Alabama, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Mark at Bennington, 1982, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Mark at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Smith, Ron and Freeman, Ann, 1989, Feb. 5, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Snodgrass, W.D. at Bennington, 1979, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Southwick, Marcia and Ted Conover, 1987, Aug. 6, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Southwick, Marcia: lecture, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Spires, Elizabeth at Stonecoast, 1981, July 21, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Spires, Elizabeth and Madison Bell, 1988, Oct. 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Spires, 1990, March 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Spires, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Stafford at Michigan, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Steinke, Darcey, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Strand, Mark at Stonecoast, 1981, July 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Strand, Mark at Stonecoast, 1982, July 12, (2 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Stuart, Dabney, 1989, April 2, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry and Carolyn Kizer, 1986, Dec. 7, (2 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1987, June 13, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry and Fred Chappell, 1992, March 7, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1993, Feb. 21, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry at Farmington, 1995, Feb. 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry and Carolyn Kizer, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry and Lynn Schwartz, at Aspen, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry: reading, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry: lecture, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry, undated, (2 tapes) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Henry: on NPR, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Taylor, Peter: Hollins Conference, 1970, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Tazewell, Widdy, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - Tillinghast, Richard: reading Sewanee in Ruins, 1984, Feb. 28, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Tillinghast, Richard at Stonecoast, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Townsend, William H., 1953, Oct. 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Ullman, Leslie at University of Texas- El Paso, 1979, Aug., (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Ullman, Leslie and Alan Cheuse at Bennington, 1981, July 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Ullman, and Cheuse, 1982, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Ullman, 1983, July 7, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Vivante, Arthur, 1979, July 13, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Voight, Ellen Bryant, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wakoski, Diane, 1984, Jan. 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Weingarten, Roger, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Weiss, Ted at Bennington, 1979, July 27, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - White, John at Bennington, 1981, July 8, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier, Allen and Katzenbach, 1979, July 20, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier, Allen at Bennington, 1982, July 27, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier, and Bell, Madison at Bennington, 1982, July 27, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier and Stephen Sandy, 1986, July 21, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier and Laura Furman, 1987, July 23, (2 tapes) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier at University of Virginia, 1988, April 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier: reading Blanco, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier: reading from Departing as Air, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wiggins, Marianne, 1993, March 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wiggins, Marianne: reading, 1993, March 11, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wilbur, Ellen at Bennington, 1981, July 7, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wilbur, Ellen, 1981, July 15, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wilbur, 1984, Sept. 25-26, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wilbur at Bennington, 1987, July 21, (2 tapes) (Box AV 7)
    - Wilks, David at Bennington, 1980, July 1, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Williams, Joy: reading, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Williams, Joy: lecture, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Willingham, Calder, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wise, Hope, 1981, July 22, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wiseman, Fred, 1988, Oct. 28, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wiseman, Fred, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wolitzer, Hilma at Bennington, 1979, July 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wolitzer at Bennington, 1981, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wolitzer, Hilma at Bennington, 1984, July 23, and Gluck, Louise at Bennington, 1984, July 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wright, Stuart at Wake Forest, 1984, April 27, and Meisel, Martin at National Humanities Center, 1984, April 26, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wright, Stuart, 1988, March 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Yates, Richard at Stonecoast, 1982, July 13, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
  - Roundtables and Panels
    - Hollins Symposium, 1970, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Slavitt and Garrett at York Harbor, 1977, June, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Party after reading at Johnson State College, 1977, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett et al., 1978, Jan. 18, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett at Hollins and Dillard at Emory, 1978, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett and Dillard at Emory, 1979, June, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett and Goerner at Bennington, 1979, July 25, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett and DelBanco at fiction workshop, 1979, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett et al. at Brown, 1979, Sept., (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett and Elman at Bennington, 1980, July 2, (2 tapes) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett and DelBanco at Bennington, 1981, June 29, (2 tapes) (Box AV 7)
    - Student reading, 1981, July 14, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Student poetry workshop at Stonecoast, 1981, July 20, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, and DelBanco at Bennington, 1981, July 29, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett and Bell at Johnson State College, 1981, July 27, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Faulkner Roundtable, 1982, Feb. 12, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett and Blanche Boyd at Bennington, 1982, July 5, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Rosen, Bell, and Garrett at Johnson State College, 1982, July 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Williams, Ciardi, and Garrett, 1982, Sept. 13, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Settle, Mary Lee and Garrett at Virginia Military Institute, 1982, Sept. 28, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett at Southern Culture, 1983, April 14, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Elman, Richard at Bennington, 1983, July 5, and Garrett and Boyd, 1983, July 29, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Student poets at Stonecoast, 1983, July 20, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Bell, Madison and Garrett, 1983, July 22, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Fiction Fellows, 1983, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett et al. at Green Mountains, 1983, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier, Allen and Garrett at Hardin-Simmons University, 1983, Nov. 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier, Allen and Garrett at Texas A&M and San Francisco State University, 1983, Nov., (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier and Garrett at Sam Houston State University, and Baylor University, 1983, Nov., (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Faulkner Panel - Modern Language Association, 1983, Dec. 29, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Nicholson and Garrett, 1983, Dec. 29, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Coffin, Lyn and Garrett at Guild House, 1984, Feb. 13, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Future Panel: Garrett et al., 1984, March 29, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Robinson, Mary and Garrett, 1984, July 1, and Flanagan, Thomas, 1984, July 2, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Robinson and Garrett, 1984, July 1, and Elman and Vivante, 1984, July 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett, 1984, July 10, and Carpenter, Bill, 1984, July 11 (Box AV 7)
    - Workshop reading, 1984, July 16, and Chute, Carolyn, 1984, July 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier, Allen and Garrett at Hardin-Simmons University, 1984, Nov. 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wier and Garrett at Hardin-Simmons, and Garrett at University of Minnesota - Duluth, 1984, Nov. 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett at Citadel, 1984, Nov. 29 and McCorkle and Cox at Michigan, 1984, Nov. 26, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Hoyns Committee, 1985, April 2, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Hagy and Garrett, 1986, Feb. 23, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Panel/Garrett, 1986, April 11, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Hearon and Garrett, 1986, July 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Bausch and Garrett, 1986, Nov. 7, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wesleyan Staff Reading, 1987, July 2, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Wolitzer and Garrett, 1987, July 22, (2 tapes) (Box AV 7)
    - Ramke and Garrett, 1987, Aug. 8, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Aldridge, John and Garrett, 1988, Jan. 21, (2 tapes) (Box AV 7)
    - Garrett, 1988, March 1, and Wright, 1988, March 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Literacy Reading, 1988, April 10, (2 tapes) (Box AV 7)
    - Clemson: Historical fiction, 1988, April 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Chappell and Garrett, 1988, April 30, (3 tapes) (Box AV 7)
    - Chappell and Garrett: Homecoming, 1988, April 30, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Taylor and Garrett, 1988, July 20, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Rogers, Tim and Garrett: talk to high school teachers, 1988, Aug. 30, (2 tapes) (Box AV 8)
    - Dunn and Garrett, 1988, Oct. 21, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Taylor and Garrett, 1988, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Literacy, 1989, April 15, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Garrett at Goucher College, 1989, April 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Steinke, 1989, May 1 and Garrett, 1989, April 30, (2 tapes) (Box AV 8)
    - Garrett et al: Capitol Hill Writers, 1989, June 4, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Garrett and others, 1989, June 4, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - NPR, 1989, June 1 and July 23, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Poets Corner, 1989, Oct. 22, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Garrett et al. at University of Virginia library, 1990, Feb. 11, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Writers, 1990, Feb. 11, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Miami Book Fair, 1990, Nov. 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Writing Life, 1991, Feb. 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Soniat and Garrett, 1991, April 9, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Florida Historical Society, 1991, May 10, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Uneasy Muses, 1991, June 8, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Heroes, 1991, Oct. 7, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Story, 1991, Nov. 23, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Dove and Garrett for SOS Reading, 1992, Sept. 22, (2 tapes) (Box AV 8)
    - Huddle and Garrett, 1992, Oct. 23, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Writers Panel, 1994, March 5, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Settle and Garrett, 1994, Oct. 14, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Richmond, 1994, Oct. 15, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Chesapeake Reading, 1995, Feb. 25, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Panel, 1995, April 1, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Q & A Panel, 1995, April 22, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Bausch and Garrett, 1995, June 1-2, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Garrett and Dillard at Emory, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Hagy and Garrett, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Leggett and Garrett at NKU, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - McAuley and Garrett, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - McAuley and Garrett at Quartz Mt., OK, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - New Letters, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Slavitt and Garrett, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Tillinghast and Garrett in Charleston, SC, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Ann Arbor preparation, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Mary Lee Settle and Garrett, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Discussion: Mueller and Garrett, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Settle and Garrett, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Sermon, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Panel:Wier, Madden, White, Cheuse, and Garrett, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Recording of New Letters Magazine, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Fiction Workshop: Spires and Carpenter, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Poet Speaks, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Music: Michigan, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Wier and Garrett at Sam Houston State University, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Trip to Maine and some poems, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Dillard at Tenn., and Garrett at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Poetry Panel, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Folger Party, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - NPR, Folger, Nicholson, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Garrett: NPR interview with Sam Vaughan, undated (Box AV 8)
    - North Dakota panel, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Ellison, Harlan, and Garrett at North Dakota, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Ellison, Garrett, et al. panel at North Dakota, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - National Humanities Center, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Future Panel and classes, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Reynolda House and Garrett, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Modern Language Association Faulkner Panel, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Dillard, Hankla, and Garrett, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Madden and Garrett at Sand Hills, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 8)
    - Roger Rath's memorial service at Johnson State College, 1980, May, (2 tapes) (Box AV 9)
    - Enchanted Ground, 1980, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - DelBanco and Garrett at Bennington, 1981, June 29, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Faulkner Panel at Sewanee, 1982, Feb. 12, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - All Things Considered, 1983, Nov. 6, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - "Coffee with the Faculty" at Michigan, 1984, April 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - NPR, 1985, Nov. 15, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Wedding, 1986, May 24 (Box AV 9)
    - Poetry, 1986, July (Box AV 9)
    - Hopwood Awards, 1988, Jan. 21, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Screenwriting Panel, 1988, Oct. 27, (2 tapes) (Box AV 9)
    - Wedding Cake, 1989, June 11-July 23, (2 tapes) (Box AV 9)
    - Poets' Corner, 1989, Oct. 22, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Charleston Panel, 1989, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Stonecoast, 1989, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Writers talking, 1990, Feb. 11, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Ft. Lauderdale Library, 1990, Oct. 2, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Heroes, 1991, Oct. 7, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Hollins, 1992, Oct. 12, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Book Reviewing, 1995, March 31, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Q & A Panel, 1995, April 22, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Bach program, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Bells of London, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Book and author dinner, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Donnell..., undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Enchanted Ground: rehearsal, undated, (2 tapes) (Box AV 9)
    - Enchanted Ground: performance, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Enchanted Ground: performance at York, Maine, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - English Club I, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - English Club II, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - English Hymns- Royal Wedding, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Fables and melodies for flute and harp, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Figure of Writer: 2, 3, & 5, (3 tapes) (Box AV 9)
    - Heroes (2), undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - John Knowles' party, Florida International University, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Literature of WWII, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - New Letters..., undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Purcell: Saint Cecelia Ode, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Soundings radio program and Nat'l Humanities Center, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - To Garrett from the King, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Welfare, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - WWSC party, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 9)
    - Photographs (Box AV 10)
    - Mini-cassettes with speeches, lectures, readings by Garrett (145 mini-tapes) (Box AV 10)
    - Mini-cassettes with readings, lectures by Garrett and others (21 mini-tapes) (Box AV 10)
    - Mini-cassettes with speeches, lectures, readings by others (177 mini-tapes) (Box AV 11)
    - Misc. mini-cassettes (41 mini-tapes) (Box AV 11)
    - Garrett interview, 1968 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Richard Wilbur at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 15 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - The Short Story Today at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 16 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Jesse Hill Ford on the film, Babcock at Hollins Conference, 1970, June 17 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Peter Taylor at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 17 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Brian Moore at Hollins Conference, 1970, June 18 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - The Publishing Scene, Parts I & II at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 18 (2 reels) (Box AV 12)
    - Brian Moore: Working with Hitchcock at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 19 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Shelby Foote at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 19 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - The Publishing Scene, Parts I & II at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 19 (2 reels) (Box AV 12)
    - William Manchester at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 20 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Hollins Conf.: Shakespeare and the Movies, 1970, June 21 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Hollins Conf: Southern Politics and Lit., Parts I & II, 1970, June 22 (2 reels) (Box AV 12)
    - Hollins Conf.: Biography, Parts I & II, 1970, June 23 (5 reels) (Box AV 12)
    - James Dickey at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 23 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Hollins Conf.: Poetry and the University Press, 1970, June 24 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - David Slavitt at Hollins Conf., 1970, June 26 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Hollins Conf.: The Scholar's Bookshelf, 1970, June (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Shelby Foote: lecture, 1970, June (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Garrett: Arizona reading, 1974, April 24 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Garrett at University of Virginia, 1975, May 17 (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Dillard and Graham: Scholar's Bookshelf, undated (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Garrett: reading Lions Everywhere, undated (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Garrett reel, undated (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Garrett: Why Work?, undated (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Story Conference, undated (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Frankenstein Meets the Space Monster, undated (1 reel) (Box AV 12)
    - Misc. cassettes, (15 tapes) (Box AV 12)
  - Lectures, Readings, and Presentations by Other Authors
    - Aiken-Taylor Award Ceremony, 1991, Jan. 14, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Ardizonne, Tony, 1982, Oct. 26, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Bausch Boys, 1988, March 27, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Bausch Boys, 1993, Sept. 12, (2 tapes) (Box AV 13)
    - Bausch, Richard, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Bausch, Robert, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Bell, Madison Smartt, 1990, March 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Bell, Madison, 1991, April 5, (3 tapes) (Box AV 13)
    - Bernays, Anne, 1993, Oct. 6, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Blair, Sydney and Debra Nystrom, 1992, April 12, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Buechner, Fred, 1992, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Buechner, Fred at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Chappell, Fred at Mary Baldwin U., 1992, Oct. 26, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Chenowith, Avery, 1991, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Cherry, Kelly, 1990, May 9, (2 tapes) (Box AV 13)
    - Cherry, Kelly, 1991, Dec. 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Cheuse, Alan, 1987, Feb. 1, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Cheuse, Alan at Williams Corner Bookstore, 1987, Sept. 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Cheuse, Alan, 1987, Nov. 7, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Chute, Carolyn at Hollins Lit. Festival, 1993, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Day, Doug, 1988, May 1, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Dillard, R.H.W. at Folger Library, early 1970s, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Dillard: reading, 1992, April 26, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Dunn, Stephen and Dave Smith, 1987, July 12, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)
    - Elman, Richard and C.E. Poverman, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 13)